(OUR FAULT)
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY
MERCEDES RON
Yes, beautiful.
FORBES
THE LEISTER HEIR CONQUERS LONDON
"IT'S BEEN A TOUGH FOUR YEARS."
CHOCOLATE WITH MILK
AND ALMONDS
No need to wrap it.
I'm going to eat it now.
Excuse me.
Sorry! I'm sorry. Shit.
Don't worry, it's not noticeable.
I'm wearing coffee-colored pants.
I always wear them when I fly.
Me, a chocolate-colored skirt.
Simón.
Noah.
Can I take you somewhere?
We can share a cab.
I'm being picked up. Thank you.
I enjoyed chatting with you.
Likewise.
Hey. I'm going to be here for a week.
If you give me your number,
perhaps one day...
I understand. As you wish.
Hey. But if we meet again,
you owe me a coffee.
Deal.
Noah! Noah!
You're here!
I'm here!
- I'm getting married!
- Yes!
Let's go.
I can't wait to show you everything.
You bridesmaids
have your dress fitting this afternoon.
Then the private party,
and tomorrow, the rehearsals.
- I'm so anxious.
- Yeah.
These are for the bridesmaids.
- It's beautiful! I love it.
- So cute!
And these masks...
They're adhesive pushups.
They go like this.
Anything for the ass?
No one can lift that ass anymore!
This is your dress, Noah.
This one? But...
This isn't a bridesmaid's dress, is it?
Those flowers don't go there.
They go in the kitchen.
Jenna. Jenna, can you explain
what's going on?
- You didn't match with my cousins.
- Sure.
The cheese corner under that tree.
- God, what a mess.
- Am I going to be the maid of honor?
Amy! Leave the dresses
and come sort things out.
- Don't do this to me, please.
- Who ordered blue tablecloths?
Who's going to be the best man?
Please understand.
You're our best friends.
No. Don't do this to me
at your wedding, please.
It's been a while. You've moved on.
The snifters go there.
You're an asshole.
This isn't right, you know?
Don't worry.
Everything is going to be great.
You know I'm an expert
in organizing parties.
Come on, let's go.
TO THE LIGHTHOUSE
VIRGINIA WOOLF
IBICENCÁN PARTY
NOAH
You're unbelievable, Jenna.
Not sure if he's my cousin or my uncle,
but he's from my family in Miami.
- Bye.
- Hi.
Those hippies lived so well in Ibiza.
You're the one living well, asshole, huh?
I'm so happy for you, brother.
That's so great.
Lion...
Jenna is looking for you
to take some pictures with her cousins.
They put me in a WhatsApp group.
"The pushups."
You didn't call me back.
What I asked you for was not for me.
It was for a friend.
You know what I mean.
You're Lion's brother.
I already was back then.
Right.
There, like that.
You look divine. Smile, everyone.
How beautiful!
Very cute. Smile, everyone!
We're like Jenna and her cousins.
We only see each other
at weddings and funerals these days.
- The restaurant takes up my weekends.
- Wonderful.
- Will!
- Me too? Yes?
Rafaella.
- Come on!
- Can you take a picture of us?
Of course. Here you go. Let's see.
What a privilege!
Ready!
JENNA LOVES LION
We're all here.
The rehearsal will be at the resort.
It's ten kilometers away.
We sent a message with the location.
Exactly. Lion, you're taking
your mother and Jenna's father.
- Nick, did you bring the child seat?
- I got it at the airport.
Terrific. Jeremy, you're going with him.
So? Ready to be my copilot?
What about me? Here?
No, go with Nick.
With Nick? No. No, please...
Long live the bride and groom! Long live!
It smells really strong.
It's my aftershave.
How was it with Nick and Noah?
Fine. It's like going with Mom and Dad.
We move forward a little bit more.
That's it. Perfect. Very good.
Now, the honor attendants.
Come on, take his arm.
On my signal, we all advance down
the aisle starting on the right foot.
Jeremy, can you take your hands
out of your pockets?
Don't we have the ring cushion?
Then bring him something to practice with.
Stay close together. All right. Ready?
Father, forgive me,
but you're in the wrong place.
I'm sorry, son.
I didn't even know blue roses existed.
You little devil! This is for grown-ups!
But it tastes like candy!
Dinner, then straight to bed!
- Hey, Luca.
- Hey.
I saw you before, but you disappeared.
I haven't seen you since you got out.
How's the garage?
Very well, brother.
I'm sorry about your grandfather.
At least he didn't suffer.
I appreciate it.
You got a tattoo?
Yes.
You're mine
Don't worry, I've also committed
the same idiocy a bunch of times. Look.
Wow. Looks like the jackpot went to Lola.
She's my mother. My one true love.
You look handsome.
Dearly beloved...
Dearly beloved, we are gathered here today
to join in holy matrimony
this man and this woman.
Welcome to all of you,
whether you are family or friends.
I take you as my wife, Jenna...
and promise to be faithful
in health, in sickness,
for richer and for poorer.
And so, to love and respect you
all the days of my life,
until death or life do us part.
Therefore, I declare you...
Husband and wife.
I love you.
Where are you going on your honeymoon?
Do you know the Seychelles?
No, I've never been.
I have a sexual fantasy that I want to...
You've chosen the destination
to satisfy a sexual fantasy?
To do it under a waterfall.
What?
Imagine it. An idyllic waterfall,
the stream of water
falling over our bodies...
Hey!
Be careful, she's my daughter.
Mr. Tavish...
That's impossible, man.
Why?
Any idea how hard the water falls?
I've already told him.
But since he saw it in that ad,
no way to get it out of his mind.
Well, fuck, let me dream, right?
It's my honeymoon.
Let the bride and groom dance!
Come on, cousin!
Just another day
Planning to get you back
The house is like hell
The memories are burning
And I like a masochist
I left everything as it was
But now that you're not here
I realized what I lost
It may not be too late
To see you and tell you
That I'm still crazy about your love
I want to tell you that I'm sorry
That I miss you
That all that's happened, baby
I regret it
I still love you
Don't think
That I've given you up for lost
I want to tell you that I'm sorry
That I miss you
That all that's happened, baby
I regret it
I still love you
Don't think
That I've given you up for lost
I wish I could reset my mind
So it doesn't think of you
But what do you want me
To do about it, baby?
I'm not gonna lie to you
It's just that
I'm drowning every second...
She must be having a terrible time.
Stop it.
How are you?
Very happy for you guys.
Sorry, my emotions are getting mixed up.
Come on. Now, the honor attendants.
I want to tell you that I'm sorry
That I miss you
That all that's happened, baby
I regret it
I still love you
Don't think that
I've given you up for lost...
Operation Honor Attendants
is proving to be pathetic.
I'll say.
They're more concerned about us
than about their own wedding.
It's not going to work.
Hi.
I found what you wrote in the cemetery.
"I will always be
your light in the darkness."
The rain will have washed it away by now.
No. Today, I saw
that light is still there.
I've seen it in your eyes.
Do you know what I see when I close them?
I see you with him.
If you leave, turn off the light.
Don't you sleep with the light on?
We can overcome everything.
Here's your degree, Ms. Graduate.
Thank you very much, María.
We're going to miss you.
Me too.
Goodbye.
WANTED FOR HIRE
DELIVERY PERSON WITH OWN VEHICLE
You're looking for
an employee with a car, right?
I'm sorry.
Hey! Are you okay?
I switched shifts with Edu.
I'll leave you the schedule, okay?
ALAMEDA
GENERAL HOSPITAL
- How are you, Alicia?
- Fine.
Good morning, Michael. Sit down.
Well...
When the boss calls you,
there's always a reason.
The bike my friend sold you, is it okay?
Yes. Amazing. Thank you.
How long have you been in mental health?
A year.
I've been reviewing your résumé,
and you didn't include
that you had worked at the university.
It was as a counselor.
I didn't think it was relevant.
Right. You got fired
for sleeping with a student, didn't you?
Ramón, you haven't had
a single problem with me.
Nor do we want to.
That's why you'll understand
we are obliged
to initiate the appropriate protocol
for these cases.
- There's nothing to investigate.
- This is not public healthcare.
We can't take the chance
that something like this
happens again with one of our clients.
Who gave you this information?
We'll keep you posted
on the progress of the case.
Thank you very much.
My first job was in insurance.
I used to bring coffee
to your grandfather.
Bastien, a company doesn't thrive
on nostalgia, it thrives on profits.
And if we don't act, we'll end up
compromising the whole law firm.
In Spain and here in London,
we'll hold up, in which case,
we'd have to say, "Bye-bye, San Francisco,
and bye-bye, Paris."
Isn't it much riskier
to start new companies?
What the hell is the met a verse?
Why do we have to invest
in these tech bubbles?
Because it's the future.
It's more cool.
Nicholas, this isn't Google,
and I'm no longer in a position
to ride a skateboard
from my office to the coffee machine.
Relax, Macías. We'll get you a wheelchair.
Hey, wait!
Coffee, anyone?
Black, with oatmeal, match a tea.
Coffee, coffee.
You can go in now.
Go in.
- I'm fine. There's nothing wrong with me.
- Restart process.
I'm really all right. Can I go?
Restart process.
Real Madrid three, Barça nil.
- You're tickling me.
- Yes, come in, sit down.
- Where are you going? No. Stop.
- I'm perfectly fine.
- Hey, cutie. Stop.
- Someday, we will rule the world.
My secretary has reviewed your résumé,
and your profile is quite interesting.
Do you know what we do?
- Yes, you...
- Stop. Hey, hey.
Stop meowing.
You create and position content
in the met a verse.
Stop meowing.
Can I get you a coffee?
- I don't want a coffee now. I don't...
- I'll go get it.
- I think...
- Stop.
I think I could contribute more
in the creative work.
To the other side. Sudo kill. Sudo kill.
- Should I come back at another time?
- No, it's already...
- Stupid humans.
- It's fixed. It was worse before.
We've met, haven't we?
The guy on the flight to Ibiza.
And the one on the motorcycle.
That was you.
I'm sorry, I didn't recognize you.
You're great at mime.
I'm telling you this as a professional,
I worked as a mime when I was young.
Yeah. Well, I guess
this is the end of the interview.
By the way, if you still have contacts
in the circus, I could use them.
As you can see,
I was born to be a dumb clown.
I take all the hits. Thank you.
Fuck, it hurts!
- Hold on. Let me see if I can...
- I can't take it anymore!
It's going to rip my tits off.
Wait! You're not going
to leave me like this?
You carry on, I'm off to the physio.
Can't you sleep?
I haven't been sleeping very well lately.
Too many things on your mind.
And you? Why aren't you sleeping?
I can't get used to this mattress.
No one else complains?
One of your friends
left this in the bathroom.
They always leave in a hurry.
By the way,
I bought curtains in New Bond Street
for the apartment in Marbella.
I'm looking forward to seeing it.
What time does your flight leave?
I was thinking of delaying it
for a couple of days.
Baxwell wants to meet with me.
He suggested I come back here.
To the London offices. What do you think?
It's not right that my personal attorney
is not a member of our firm.
Why don't you accept our offer?
Having you as my boss
would be the last thing on my list.
Hey, you didn't tell me in the end
if you saw Noah at the wedding.
Yes, we didn't talk much.
I'm going down to the gym.
USING THE PRINTER IS FORBIDDEN,
EVERYTHING IS VIRTUAL
- You left Martín's mandalas behind again.
- Thanks, Noah.
- Is he still nervous at school?
- Yes.
If he continues like this,
I'll have to buy a printer.
May I?
Come in. I was checking your corrections.
The sales clerk is much friendlier now.
And it sells better,
which is what matters.
Good job, but it was for tomorrow.
- Right.
- What about Amazon Music?
It's been on your avatar's computer
for a week. An Easter egg.
Are you trying to impress me?
Actually, it's been there for a month.
Do you remember the plane where we met?
I was traveling
to meet with new investors.
We need to expand.
I presented our strategic plan...
but it didn't work.
I want you to improve it.
But I'm neither a consultant
nor an economist.
It's not a content problem.
I think it's the arguments that fail.
EXPANSION PLAN
I don't know,
try structuring it differently.
Things are getting difficult
for the promising Leister heir.
Today marks two days of protests
since the announcement of the closure
of one of the most emblematic companies
of the Spanish holding company.
The workers received
the letter of dismissal
without anyone realizing
that the company had financial problems.
JOBS
LET'S STOP UNJUSTIFIED DISMISSALS
William, please.
Have you spoken to your son yet?
You're a crook!
Thief!
You've destroyed my family,
you crook! Crook!
You're going to pay,
you crook, you thief...
Let's get out of here, please.
WE ARE NOT DISPOSABLE
UNITED FOR JUSTICE
Yes, this is how
they fire people at Leister.
They're not content
to just give us the boot.
You have four kids
and you just got into a mortgage, right?
We need to turn back the clock.
We can't.
We'll transfer most of the people
once we open the new headquarters.
But you know that it's his son
who runs the company from London now.
But he doesn't have the balls
to show his face.
We need to distract shareholders
from all this.
Use the tabloids. Set up an NGO.
Whatever, but you have to do it now.
He thinks I'm your wife.
You would be the perfect wife for anyone.
My parents think the same about you.
Should we see less of each other
so they don't get their hopes up?
On the contrary.
I think we should formalize
our relationship.
Sorry?
I'm tired of picking up cheap lingerie
around my apartment.
Besides, we're both interested.
We're interested?
The election is coming up soon.
Your father is running again.
For show, he'll need you
to have a formal partner.
You want to leak to the press
that we're together.
That we're dating.
Okay, what's in it for you?
I may be in need
of a change of image myself.
Yes, you're right. It wouldn't hurt you
to look a little more human.
I didn't think I was going to like
the place so much.
- Yeah, me neither. I didn't know it.
- Dinner was good...
- Very tasty, indeed.
- The silverware was beautiful.
And dessert. The dessert was quite good.
I'm sorry, I started to eat
and I didn't leave you anything.
You have a stain here.
I should have worn
the chocolate-colored blouse.
I don't know, Simón.
I think I'd rather go a little slower.
Me too, but I didn't dare tell you.
Right.
- And for dessert, a rejection.
- No, silly.
Another day.
Hey, the print toner has run out
and I don't know how.
- Do you know anything?
- No, I don't.
And this cactus?
It gives me positive energy.
You've sucked it all out
and only left the negative one.
Tomorrow, the investors can't see this.
Guys, I told you.
I want your desks spotless.
Not too serious, not too geeky.
When does Mr. Scrooge arrive?
- 8:00 a.m.
- So early?
Will we have time
to roll out the red carpet?
In the end, is it one investor or several?
Do you want to know how many coffees
you have to prepare?
Me, huh? Okay.
Well then, whoever loses makes the coffee.
- I bet you 20 bucks Noah wins.
- Come on.
Let's see...
Whenever you want.
What are you doing here?
I've just bought shares in this company.
Yeah, well, I work here,
so I'm afraid I'm part of the package.
You should focus
on your postgraduate degree.
I'm capable of doing both.
What's going on?
How do you know each other?
I've invested millions in a company.
Not in an Irish pub.
- Sorry.
- What is my stepsister's position?
- She is a systems assistant.
- Coffees and photocopies, right?
We don't make photocopies here.
Look, the strategic plan you liked so much
was written by her.
She's very good
and has a lot of potential, you know?
I don't doubt it. But you do make coffee,
don't you? Can she bring me one?
Hi, Sof.
Hey! I thought we were eating out today.
Was your flight delayed?
No, but something told me
I had to pass by the new company.
It's chaos. I think I'm going
to have to stay longer than I thought.
We're still a trending topic.
I know. And the stock continues to rise.
It looks like our plan was a success.
Like everything we do together, dear.
All right.
By the way, the new mattress has arrived.
Do you want to try it?
- I'm sure it's fine.
- Come here.
Sara.
Thanks.
Hey, sorry about the nickname.
It was just to call him something.
It was confidential.
I couldn't say his name.
Don't worry, Mr. Scrooge is spot-on.
Can you print out my exercise chart?
I don't have time to go
to the gym this week.
Coffee. Coffee. Does anybody want coffee?
Black? With oatmeal? Matcha tea.
So, are you going to go out with him?
Well, maybe.
I don't know, he's funny, kind, calm...
Predictable.
Don't be mean. He's cute.
And Nick?
- I'm over Nick.
- No.
- I have to turn over a new leaf.
- And you think that's easy?
Well, yes, as easy as doing this.
EXCLUSIVE: THE GOLDEN BACHELOR
SETTLES DOWN
THE LOVE STORY
THAT HAS MOVED EVERYONE
I should have kept quiet.
- Did you know about this?
- Lion told me yesterday.
Michael? How's it going?
I haven't seen you in...
Yes. Very well.
Is something wrong?
Would you mind
leaving me in peace, please?
Sorry, I just wanted...
You're just fucking up my life.
It was just a fucking fling.
Don't tell your little brother
you've seen me.
I don't want more problems.
The defendant was videotaped
from the window of the adjoining building.
You go on.
Your Honor, cameras do not lie.
Hi, Sofía, did I catch you at a good time?
Yes, I was on a break.
I wanted to talk to you about something
that I'd rather not discuss
directly with Nick.
And since you're now his... lawyer...
Don't worry. What's it all about?
Do you remember Michael?
My faculty counselor.
Yes.
What's your relationship with him?
Nothing serious.
I may have pulled a few strings.
That matter has nothing to do
with you guys. It only concerns me.
That guy was a bastard. He and Briar...
If anyone screwed up, it was me.
So, please, I'm asking you
to leave him alone.
Okay.
- Pretty, huh?
- Very much, Petra.
Thanks for coming.
I was looking forward to seeing Maggie
after such a long time.
Since it's the first time she's staying
to sleep and she adores you...
I hope she remembers me.
I'm sure she does.
The poor thing can't comprehend
that she's Will's daughter.
And, frankly, neither can I.
Every time I think
about what happened that night...
It's forgotten now.
Forgetting is not the same as forgiving.
- Do I look okay like this? Yes, right?
- You look very handsome.
- Don't worry.
- No, Petra, Maggie can't eat this.
She can, it has agave syrup.
Don't worry.
I've made it hundreds of times
for my husband, who is also diabetic.
Hi.
Hello, daughter. How was your trip? Good?
Noah!
Maggie!
Hi, sweetie. You look so grown up,
and pretty. I love your dress.
Okay, ready? One, two, three.
Pull, pull, pull! All right!
You had an appetite, huh?
So much so that I'm going
to take another piece.
Can I have more too?
Yes, of course. I'll get it for you.
- You want some?
- I'll go with you.
Hey, while you're at it,
can you get me a coffee?
"The financial shark
devouring his own empire."
What good does it do you to have a board
if you don't take their advice?
What your grandfather
taught you is enough, right?
You think the modern thing to do
is to act with an iron fist.
Here. You take them.
Right. Thanks.
Here.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I'd love to go to the party. Where is it?
Do you want us to light the tree?
Watch. You'll see.
Everything is controlled here.
From the phone, see?
Man, I love that place.
The avatars go crazy.
Do you want me to install the app
on your phone?
Nick, can you help me?
- What a pity.
- One moment.
I don't have my VR goggles.
See? This turns it off and on.
Okay, that'll be best. Talk to you later.
Your boss calls you outside of work.
That's not very professional.
Same for you. What's my supreme boss
doing trying to control my private life?
You're my sister here.
Too bad you can't give me orders here.
Nick!
Just a moment, dear.
Let your father help you.
Asshole.
Damn syrup.
As the memo that has reached you says,
all subsidiaries of the Leister Group
must abide by the same regulations.
It's silly, because I know
that many of you are not affected,
but from now on, fraternization
between employees is strictly forbidden.
So as not to be unfair, if there is
any relationship already started,
now is the time to say so.
That's all. Thank you very much.
I hope this has nothing to do with Noah,
but I think
you should have consulted me first.
I knew you were a bad negotiator
when you dumped so many shares.
Now I see that you are also
a bad strategist.
Because you're giving yourself away.
It's the same as last time.
I don't know if you liked it.
I shouldn't try it again.
It's an Olivia, the best French wine.
Hey, before you go bankrupt because of me,
maybe we should talk about Nick.
You don't want anything with him anymore.
He needs to accept it.
He just won't stop. He's looking
for any excuse to throw you out.
From your own company, Simón.
I don't know. Maybe we should stop.
I don't give a shit about my company.
I'm not giving up on you.
Elevator doors opening.
Elevator doors closing.
I've had them installed
throughout the office.
They're recording 24/7.
Gotta make sure
the rules are followed, right?
Yes, I'm sorry. I've made my decision.
I'm going to do it.
It's settled.
- I'm sorry.
- Think about it.
- No, Simón.
- At least think about it.
It's the only solution.
I've already decided, okay? I'm sorry.
Here's my letter of resignation.
Are you going to make a scene
like an angry teenager?
I couldn't care less.
That's your problem.
You can't stop seeing me
as if I were still that teenager.
Aren't you the same?
I would say you are.
The same eyes.
The same lips.
Same hair.
Same tattoo.
Be careful, there are cameras.
Just as sarcastic.
You're pathetic at trying to be
the same one you were back then.
Why do you want to leave?
If I have to choose,
I'd rather quit my job.
So there's something between you.
Look, I'm with Simón.
Accept it just like I accept
that you're with Sofía.
Who told you I'm with her?
Fuck, all that's left
is to put ads on bus shelters.
- Have you slept with him?
- And you with her?
How many women since we broke up,
including myself?
So you have.
You can't reject me and then demand
that no one touch me.
You have no feelings for him. I know it.
If you don't know how to forgive,
learn to accept.
Sometimes, the prey escapes the shark too.
No, Morti, I can take it.
No, miss, it's my duty.
It's been a great vacation.
Excuse me. If we want to make it,
we have to leave now.
Yes.
Nick has to take me.
I think he must have had some problem,
but I can go with you, huh?
Noah would be better. Can you?
Sure, of course.
Shall we go in my car? Come on.
I didn't know your mother was coming.
Why don't you come and see us one day?
You can come alone.
- Sounds perfect to me.
- Maggie!
- I'm sorry. I couldn't get here sooner.
- You are very busy. It's all right.
Hello, son.
What are you doing here?
Nicholas, give me five minutes, please.
It's about Maggie.
No fucking way.
Nick, talk to her. Please.
I want a Green Juice.
And my zipper won't close,
but a Bridget Jones.
- Uh-huh.
- Thanks.
Five minutes. Not one more.
I'm going to give custody of Maggie
to her father.
Which father?
Yours. To William.
- Are you going to abandon her like me?
- Don't worry. I'm not abandoning her.
Then why the hell do you want
to give away her custody for?
I'm sick, Nick.
What do you mean, sick?
I have leukemia.
I've been struggling
with the disease for four years.
So, when you put on that little show
at the gala, you knew.
I just wanted to protect Maggie.
To let your father know
she was his daughter. To let you know.
Why should I trust you
after all you've done to us?
Nick, I don't have much time left.
Your father and I have already
signed everything.
Maggie was going to come back with me,
but I got an urgent call for surgery,
so I'm afraid you're going to have
to take her back with you.
B.
This isn't fair to her.
I know you hate me,
but take care of Maggie.
Do it for her.
- How are you, my love?
- Good.
- You're going back with Nick, okay?
- Okay.
To the house. I've got things to do.
You know how much I love you?
If Maggie needs anything, you know...
I don't want to be alone tonight.
Please.
It will only make things worse.
Things can't get any worse.
Nick!
She's gone.
She came to give me a kiss.
- Good morning. How do you feel?
- Much better, thanks.
Are you taking iron?
No.
Hasn't your gynecologist prescribed
any vitamin supplements?
No.
Have you been tested for toxoplasmosis?
Not that either.
Why should I have it done?
It's the most advisable thing to do
when you're pregnant.
Pregnant?
You didn't know.
How?
What you have is an intrauterine hematoma.
That's why you're here.
It's what was causing the bleeding
that you may have mistaken
for menstruation.
No, but that's impossible.
You're 16 weeks pregnant.
Sixteen weeks? No, but I...
I just, right now...
- It's impossible.
- You have a high-risk pregnancy,
so we're going to have to do
a couple more ultrasounds, okay?
Don't worry, because we're going
to take great care of you.
OFFICE 03
DR. LAURA GARCÍA
PATIENTS
NOAH MORÁN
SECOND TRIMESTER
OBSTETRIC ULTRASOUND REPORT
NOAH MORÁN PRADA
WEEKS OF GESTATION: XVI
FATHER'S DETAILS: NOT PROVIDED
Sixteen weeks.
Four months.
You have to tell him.
No fucking way.
What do you mean? He's the father.
He has a right to know.
Do you know how many genes
the X chromosome contributes?
Nine hundred.
And do you know how many
the Y contributes?
Fifty-five.
For the little they contribute,
do you think it's worth
telling the father?
That's very deep, girl.
- Thanks.
- Well, no!
- Nonsense is what it is.
- Really...
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Did you say XY?
Is it going to be a boy?
Oh, God!
Well, we'll have to get ready.
First of all, you need rest,
so you're going to leave your shitty flat
and come here with us.
And while you're painting your room
and the baby's room,
you'll stay in the guest room.
You're not even going
to let me take it in?
I'm going to be an aunt. "Aunt Jenna."
Sounds like an old lady, but glamorous.
I'm starting to tingle.
I'm already starting to get excited.
You'll see how excited
Grandma Rafaella will be.
What a day I've had, my love.
I'll tell you about it later, huh?
Guess who's pregnant?
What? How?
Oh, my God, dude. Damn, dude.
Fucking Seychelles waterfalls!
Really? Damn...
It's not me, you idiot. It's Noah.
Shit, what a scare!
So whose is it?
Remember Operation Honor Attendants?
Well, now it's bearing fruit.
And never better said.
Look at me. You can't say anything.
Lion.
- Nick doesn't know?
- No.
And why are you telling me first, dude?
You know how... Wrong!
- So wrong, Jenna!
- Why?
Because you know I suck
at keeping secrets. I struggle.
I'm not going to be able to, Jenna.
Now it's inside me...
Do you want me to tell Nick how well
the waterfall went?
I thought so.
You're a blackmailer.
- I love you!
- Blackmailer!
The surgeons have the special menu
and the psychologists and nurses
have the normal lunch.
But that's not enough for them.
We also have to sit separately.
Look... I've worked myself to the bone
to get here.
I'm sorry about the case,
but there's nothing we can do.
Do you know who's the bigger shareholder
of the company
to which this hospital belongs?
The Leister insurance company.
Which has just been liquidated.
We no longer have
the authority to intervene.
What if I ask Noah?
Maybe Nick will listen to her
more than to you.
They no longer have much
of a relationship.
Really? It was my understanding
that they now work together at LRB.
Didn't you know that?
And they must have seen each other before.
Otherwise, I don't know
how this would be possible.
They both posted stories
at Jenna's wedding.
Date-wise, it's a match.
I hope the press doesn't find out.
Imagine the headlines.
"Nicholas Leister, the model businessman,
the perfect boyfriend,
gets his stepsister pregnant."
And I'm not just talking
about the shares of his companies.
How would it affect
your father's election campaign
if a scandal broke
about his future son-in-law?
You'll see how much fun it is.
When Nick finds out,
he'll run like a puppy into her arms.
I think I'm going to stay
in the hospital for a while.
If you feel you need help
from a professional,
don't hesitate to make an appointment.
How's your son, Esteban?
Good. Adjusting to the new school.
Ah, no. I wasn't talking about Tony.
I was talking about Aaron.
Aaron?
He's good too.
He's in marketing, isn't he?
In a subsidiary of yours.
No. He got promoted to another company.
Of the group?
Yes, from the group too.
Which one?
The insurance company.
He's out of a job?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me before?
- Don't worry. Next week, I'll call and...
- No. Don't bother.
It's useless. He got in on his own merits
and you know him.
He's very proud.
He's not going to accept any favors.
I swear I didn't know that.
I really didn't.
Don't worry, sir.
What's Noah doing here?
I think she is dating Simón.
Nick. Hello. Come with me.
Simón!
A handshake to seal the merger.
- I see you came with your girlfriend.
- And you with yours.
Noah. How are you?
- Fine.
- You look very elegant.
You are more than elegant, as always.
I talked to Michael.
It's all taken care of.
Thank you.
I didn't know how Nick would react,
so I chose to come to you.
You did the right thing.
There are some things Nick is better off
not knowing, don't you think?
You're dancing.
No. I'm holding back the urge to pee.
You can go to the bathroom.
I'll wait for you here.
No, it doesn't matter.
They're usually pretty dirty anyway.
I've never seen you dance before.
Okay. I'll be right back.
Barman. Give me another one of these.
Is the choreography yours?
Very funny. What do you want?
Nothing. Are you okay?
Great.
Hey, I've been thinking
about everything that's been going on
at the company with the cameras, and...
I went a little off the deep end.
I hope it was recorded.
When you want, you can come back to work.
You know how I hate your aftershave.
Is that why you left the other morning
without saying anything?
I left because I don't like
being walked out on twice,
so it was my turn.
- You don't know what I was going to say...
- Are you having a good time, Leister?
There was a long line at the bathroom.
- This is Sofía.
- Wow.
Nice to meet you.
You're so beautiful, oh, my.
Congrats. You're going to have
beautiful children.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Hey, I've seen how you dance,
and you have style.
But you need to loosen up a bit, girl.
Come on, I'll teach you.
You just need to loosen up a little...
What the hell are you doing?
I still can't control myself
when I'm around you, Freckles.
It's been happening to me forever.
I'm going to the bar for a moment.
- One second.
- Okay.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I think I ate something that made me sick.
I want to go home. Can you call Simón?
Simón's in no condition to drive.
Okay? Come on, let's go.
Why are you staying
at Jenna and Lion's house?
Because my landlord raised my rent.
I remind you that I am now unemployed.
Boy, what happened to you? Did you eat N?
He's become a gourmet.
I'll help you. Wait.
If you want, I can stay on the couch.
Please, let's not continue with this game.
We're not the same anymore.
We've rebuilt our lives.
You're going to start a family with Sofía,
the person you love.
It's what your parents have always wanted.
She's really great.
And it's true,
you will have beautiful children.
It could have been the same
or better with you.
Could you be the father of my children
without forgiving me?
I think this is the moment
when our story really ends.
I don't want it to end like this.
Goodbye, Nick.
Goodbye, Freckles.
Breathe. You took too long to come here.
YOUR CHILDREN NICK AND MAGGIE
Hello, brother.
I'm sorry.
Poor Maggie.
It's unfair to her.
She's always been afraid of being alone.
Sir.
- Thank you, Martín. Just a minute.
- Okay.
Maggie, look what I found.
It was my favorite toy when I was a kid.
It's a collector's item, you know?
Nick used to love playing with it.
It's just that, well,
I never gave it to him. Do you want it?
No, thank you. There's no need.
Wow, that's cool. May I?
Yes, of course.
Stop!
You look unwell.
We're at a funeral.
Everybody looks unwell.
Oh. You have a fever.
I don't know.
I must be coming down with something, Mom.
Careful. It's a collector's item
and you'll break it!
What do you care if it's not even yours?
It's William's,
and what's his is mine, right, Will?
Yes, of course it's yours,
but you can also share it, hmm?
Hey! Are you okay?
I hate him.
Don't say that.
William loves you very much.
If he loved me,
he wouldn't agree with him.
Well, loving someone doesn't mean
giving in to their every whim.
Sometimes, you have to know how to say no,
and William is your father...
No! He's not! My dad left because of him
and he didn't even come today.
You know,
it's almost never one person's fault.
And when you understand that,
you learn to forgive.
I know William loves us both
very much, don't you?
We can't spend our lives rejecting
those who love us, can we?
Come on, go back to your cousins.
Here.
Thanks.
Avoid the caramelized onion. It has syrup.
Hey, when I talked to Michael...
Did you know he works at the hospital?
What hospital?
He has access to your medical records.
What does he know?
Enough.
You won't be able to hide it much longer.
What's your plan?
Tomorrow, I'm going to Santander
to an aunt of mine.
That's a long way away.
When are you coming back?
I don't intend to return.
Anything you need, you can count on us.
- Good night.
- Bye.
Well, we sisters are going to sleep.
Because we're sisters now,
did you know that?
It's true.
Bye.
Thank you, honey.
Good night, Dad.
Good night, Noah.
Bye, Dad.
Good night, daughter.
Can you hear the sea?
I love to close my eyes
and hear the waves.
It's like feeling
that someone is rocking you.
You know?
This room is like a huge conch shell.
You can always hear the sea
even if it's quiet.
You never feel alone in here.
Do you like my room?
I love it.
Well, as of today, it's yours.
What about you?
Me... Well, make room for me when I come.
The bed is very big.
Thank you.
Thank you, honey. I love you.
Hi.
Come in.
You came from the funeral?
Has his mother's death softened him up
or is he still a bastard?
Hey, I wanted to tell you that...
I missed you.
We talk every day.
Wait. I have to tell you something.
What?
Remember the MKO reporter?
There's been a staffing adjustment.
My father needed to give his campaign
a boost and bought shares in the channel.
When are the elections?
Next week. Why?
I was thinking of selling my apartment.
Aren't you coming back?
Are you trying to tell me something?
I think it's better to break up now
while there's still time.
Still time?
Of course. I've been a fool.
I'm sorry.
You can't forget Noah, can you?
The truth is, the gesture she had
with Maggie was incredible.
I should have done it a long time ago.
Impossible. You're incapable
of hugging your father.
Your resentment prevents you
from doing so.
Resentment?
It's the only thing that drives your life.
Yes, Nick, the resentment.
You blame your father
for letting your mother leave.
And what do you do?
You punish him by dismantling
his way of running the company.
His style is not very profitable.
But it's more humane.
And then you punished your mother
without wanting to listen to her.
My mother is dead.
And what have you done? Tell me,
what did you do to stop her from leaving?
Nothing.
Look around you, Nick.
Everyone has forgiven but you.
All you have left is Noah.
And you know why you don't forgive her?
Because if you open your heart again,
you risk heartbreak,
but that's what living is, Nick.
Living is risking pain.
- Do you think I don't suffer?
- Really?
You've always had others
do your dirty work for you.
First your grandfather. Yes. Then me.
But I can't take it anymore.
You have to face your problems alone.
To keep you safe,
everyone else gets screwed.
- I never wanted to hurt you.
- Well, you have.
You've hurt us all.
Especially Noah.
When you've forgiven her, go see her.
And don't try to hold on to Maggie
to make sense of your life,
because she doesn't need you anymore.
The only one who needs you right now
is Noah, believe me.
Why are you doing this?
I don't even know why I'm doing it myself.
Thank you, Sof. I love you too.
- Let me try this here.
- No.
- Let's see what it tastes like.
- You've already eaten yours. No!
Yes?
Simón! How is the new LRB headquarters
coming along?
I've decided to move to London
to be a little more hands-on.
You're leaving?
There's nothing keeping me here.
The new headquarters
must be put into operation
right now, with all the staff.
With workers?
Yes. From the insurance company.
The Sales force is left out,
but at least we can recycle everything.
Marketing, IT and Accounting.
That's crazy. You can't use my company
to fix your screw-ups.
It's in the agreement you signed.
We both know the relocation was an excuse.
I was always very serious about it.
So now you care about others? Sure.
Hey, Ramón,
tell your friend that the bike's batteries
degrade very fast, huh?
You have to charge them only up to 80%.
Then I can't make it to work.
Well, that doesn't matter anymore.
The conclusions of the case.
No. No, no, no. It seems to me
that there's been a mistake.
They should have called you.
Please, sign and let's end this
as soon as possible.
In a peaceful manner.
Five milligrams is fine.
We'll check tomorrow.
Thank you.
Hi, Michael. She's stable.
We've controlled the bleeding.
Apparently, she's had
a similar episode in the past.
She keeps telling me about her son,
but I don't see anything in her file.
I didn't dare sedate her.
I wanted you to examine her first.
All yours.
Hi, Briar.
Michael! It's great to see you.
I can't believe you're leaving.
Yeah.
Goodbye, baby.
Thank you.
Let's see where we can put this one now.
Not in the trunk, you animal!
Who let it slip?
I swear I didn't.
- Lion?
- Seriously?
I got a stomach ulcer from keeping quiet!
Noah!
What are you doing here?
Are you going somewhere?
It's none of your business.
- I know it's none of my business, I just...
- Each to his own path.
And I try, but here I am.
All paths lead me to you.
That's a nice phrase,
but it's just a phrase.
If you don't have
anything new to say, I'm going.
Listen. Move, man.
Hey, you haven't even said hello.
- How are you? Good?
- Good.
- What about my kiss? Wait!
- Listen!
You're the woman who... Get out of the way.
Okay, I don't want to interfere
in such an awkward situation.
Will you stop? You're making me dizzy.
I want us to start from scratch.
Just you and me.
Just the two of us?
That's impossible.
Impossible why?
This is an awkward situation indeed.
Will you guys explain it to me?
You asked for it.
What is that?
Is it clear to you now? Great, I'm going.
- You're...
- Yes, she is.
Okay, it's fine, it's okay.
I don't care.
Okay, fine.
Since you don't care, I'll leave.
No, wait. I do care,
it's just I wasn't expecting it.
Wait! Noah, please.
Please don't go.
Noah, forgive me. I love you.
I don't care about anything else,
and I mean anything.
I don't even care that it's Simón's.
Simón's?
- I'll love it as if it were my own!
- It is yours, you idiot!
What? Noah!
Congratulations.
Sure, man. Get in.
- Keys, come on!
- Okay, okay.
That felt so good.
This thing won't go faster, fuck.
How beautiful.
Beautiful? But it was torture.
Come on!
Noah!
Roll down the window!
What's the matter, Nick?
With all those chauffeurs
you forgot how to drive?
How far along are you?
Twenty-four weeks.
How much is that in months?
- Six months.
- Six months?
Six months?
At the wedding?
Yeah, don't do any more math,
Nick, it's yours.
So... I'm going to be a father!
Yes.
No. I'm going to be a mother.
Shit!
You can't walk away and throw me aside.
You can take your 55 genes
and take them with you.
It won't be very noticeable anyway.
Fuck.
Are you leaving the city?
Yes.
You can't do that.
And why not?
National Geographic
included it in its list
of the most charming places in the world!
Too many forest fires.
I love you.
Come on, look ahead.
You have to pay us alimony.
Yes, please.
Wait. You're going to the mansion?
I can't leave without telling my mother
that she's going to be a grandmother.
Nick?
Nick! Nick!
Nick! Nick! Nick.
Nick!
Hey! Hey, you!
Nick! Please, I'm here with you,
okay, my love? I'm here.
I've been stupid. I deserve it.
It's all my fault, Freckles.
No, enough with looking
for people to blame. Enough.
Nick! Nick, Nick, Nick!
I'm here, I'm here, look at me.
Open your eyes, okay?
Esteban! Esteban!
- I've called an ambulance.
- No!
I'm not going to lose you again, Nick.
Please.
No, please. Please.
- My son!
- Nick!
Nick. My love. Are you all right?
Hi, Freckles.
What happened?
You've had a very long nap.
Son, you've been in a coma.
How much time has passed?
It's amazing.
I didn't know babies were so relaxing.
He's perfect.
He's the most beautiful baby
I've ever seen.
I can't believe
you're finally here with us.
You've done everything very well.
Even the house. Our house.
It's perfect.
You've made me the happiest man
in the world, Freckles.
Remember when we first kissed in that car?
I was so nervous
that my whole body was shaking.
And you were gorgeous.
Was it for me?
I give you my heart again, Freckles.
It looks like the one I gave you
five years ago, but it's not.
Now it has a little detail in the middle.
- Wait, I'll help you.
- Don't worry.
- Dad should go to sleep for a while.
- More?
More. Isn't that right, my love?
Rest.
Goodbye, Mommy. Goodbye.
Don't worry, it's just the storm.
Briar.
It's my turn. You go back to sleep.
What are you doing here?
He just needs to be rocked.
Listen. Put the baby down, okay?
There, there, little one.
Little star, where are you?
In the sky or in the sea?
A real diamond
Little star, where are you?
I wonder who you are
In the sky or in the sea
A real diamond
Little star, where are you?
In the sky or in the sea?
Yes, Nick. Mommy's here.
He's got your eyes.
It's all right.
You're handsome, huh? But not very smart.
Nick!
No!
Noah!
Briar, let my son go.
Your son? He's mine now.
What are you saying?
You owe me. A son for a son.
We don't owe you anything, okay?
I won't allow you to enjoy
what I didn't have. No.
Please.
Come on. Go down.
No, Briar!
- Briar!
- Go on!
- Let her go!
Briar!
Let her go, you son of a bitch!
First, you get me kicked out of college.
Then from the hospital.
No one is going to hire me
with my background.
So I give up. You guys won.
Soon I'll be out of this fucking country
and you won't see me again.
What's wrong, Nick?
Where is that bully inside you now?
- Get off!
- Stop, damn it!
Briar! Briar! Briar!
Thor. Thor, come on, inside.
Come on! Go inside.
Briar, please don't hurt him.
Don't do this to us.
Don't worry.
I'm going to give him lots of love.
You need help.
I know. That's why I have Michael.
You know what? You could use a scar.
Your face is too pretty.
It would give you character.
And you know something else?
Yeah?
If Thor senses you're threatening me,
he'll tear you to pieces.
You know,
I've always hated you since college.
Nick!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
They say that
when you come close to dying,
your whole life flashes
before your eyes like in a movie.
Or like in a book.
Before my eyes...
I've always had yours.
When it wasn't what we wanted...
When we started playing around...
When we couldn't help ourselves...
When other people tried to stop us...
You're mine
That gaze
always kept us connected.
Until today.
Therefore, I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
- Hooray!
- Long live the newlyweds!
- Gorgeous!
- That's my brother!
You're beautiful!
One, two... and three!
Thank you.
In the email you'll find
the airline tickets,
- the ferry tickets...
- And everything will be perfect.
Let's go, Noah.
Hey, Nick! I sent you
the location of the waterfall.
Goodbye, my love!
Hey, not so fast!
Change of plans.
No.
What a machine!
I owed you one.
Hey! You haven't recovered yet.
Besides, I'm going to spend
my whole life working
to pay off that loan, so I'm driving.
You don't believe it yourself.
You're still having aftereffects, see?
Thank you, guilty, for being always there.
Everything that will happen from now on
will be your fault...